<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Aqita Partners</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password (optional)</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>

    <string name="default_media_location_folder">Aqita Partners</string>

    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_splash">SplashActivity</string>


    <string name="application_key">2f5889429834046949516164f3617897</string>


    <string name="internet_connection_not_available">No internet connection</string>

    <string name="menu_search">Search</string>
    <string name="menu_add_contact">Create a new contact</string>
    <string name="menu_edit_contact">Edit Contact</string>
    <string name="no_contacts">No Contacts Found</string>
    <string name="no_contact_selected">No Contact Selected</string>
    <string name="search_hint">Email, userId, number</string>
    <string name="activity_contacts_list">MobiTexter</string>
    <string name="activity_contacts_title">Select contact</string>
    <string name="activity_contact_detail">Contact Detail</string>
    <string name="contacts_list_search_results_title">Contact search for \"%s\"</string>
    <string name="contactsListActivity">Contact List</string>
    <string name="phone_number_not_present">Phone number is not present</string>
    <string name="mobiframework_title_device">Device</string>
    <string name="mobiframework_title_group">Group</string>
    <string name="zero_friends_on_phone">No matching contact found on phone contacts but you can still send message by entering the email, userId or phone number</string>
    <string name="contact_sync_in_progress">Contact sync is in progress, might take few mins</string>
    <string name="zero_friends_on_mobitexter">No contacts on mobitexter</string>
    <string name="zero_groups_on_phone">No groups, add groups in your mobile or gmail account</string>
    <string name="delete_thread_text">Deleting....</string>


    <!--
         Used for the AlphabetIndexer in ContactsListFragment to provide quick navigation by
         alphabet using ListView fast scroll.
    -->
    <string name="alphabet">ABCDEFGHIJKLMNOPQRSTUVWXYZ</string>

    <string name ="last_seen_at_time">Last seen</string>
    <string name="is_typing">is typing...</string>
    <string name="user_online">Online</string>


    <!--
         When using ContactsContract.Contacts#CONTENT_FILTER_URI to search contacts, a match occurs
         when using a number of different fields, such as name, e-mail address, address, phone
         number, etc. When a match occurs that is not the name, there is currently no way to tell
         which other field was matched. This string is displayed in the secondary display text in
         ContactsListFragment when a search query match occurs that is not the display name.
    -->
    <string name="search_match_other">Matches Other Field</string>
    <string name="invite">Invite your friends</string>
    <array name="alphabet_color">
        <item>#f16364</item>
        <item>#f58559</item>
        <item>#f9a43e</item>
        <item>#e4c62e</item>
        <item>#67bf74</item>
        <item>#59a2be</item>
        <item>#2093cd</item>
        <item>#ad62a7</item>
    </array>
    <dimen name="tile_letter_font_size">250dp</dimen>
    <!-- The deafult tile size -->
    <dimen name="letter_tile_size">64dp</dimen>

    <string name="send_text">SEND</string>
    <string name="cancel_text">CANCEL</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="terms_condition">TERMS AND CONDITIONS \n\n

Aqita Technologies Pvt Ltd, a Private Limited Company under the Companies Act, 1956

having its office at 10/7, Meanee Avenue Road, Ulsoor, who is the owner of the mobile

application Aqita Partners (the “Application Provider”) reserves all rights not expressly

granted to you under these Terms and Conditions. Aqita Partners mobile application, the

product that is subject to these Terms and Conditions is hereafter referred to as the

“Licensed Application”.\n\n

Scope of License\n

This license granted to you for the Licensed Application by the Application Provider, is

limited to a non-exclusive, non-transferable, license to use the Licensed Application on

any Android™ device that you own or control. This license does not allow you to use the

Licensed Application on any Android™ device that you do not own or control, and you

may not distribute or make the Licensed Application available over a network where it

could be used by multiple devices at the same time. Nothing contained in the Licensed

Application should be considered as granting you, by implication or otherwise, any

license or right to use any trade-marks, logos, or other names contained in the Licensed

Application. You may not rent, lease, lend, sell, redistribute or sublicense the Licensed

Application. You may not copy, decompile, reverse engineer, disassemble, attempt to

derive the source code of, modify, or create derivative works of the Licensed Application,

any updates, or any part thereof (except as and only to the extent any foregoing

restriction is prohibited by applicable law or to the extent as may be permitted by the

licensing terms governing use of any open sourced components included within the

Licensed Application). Any attempt to do so is a violation of the rights of the Application

Provider and its licensors. If you breach this restriction, you may be subject to

prosecution and damages. The terms of the license will govern any upgrades provided by

the Application Provider that replace and/or supplement the original Licensed Application,

unless such upgrade is accompanied by a separate license in which case the terms of

that license will govern its use.\n\n

User Access and Consent to Use of Data\n

By downloading and registering with the Licensed Application, you represent that you are

not barred by any law, in any jurisdiction or bound by any agreement that restricts your

rights to access, download and register with the Licensed Application, to provide services

to and receive payments from customers who use the Aqita application belonging to the

Application Provider.\n

In order to register with the Licensed Application you will have to provide your mobile

number, name (in the event that your business is a sole proprietorship and the business

is in your personal name), and business name. You will ensure that the mobile number

provided for registration with the Licensed Application is your own and does not belong

to any third party and that it is a valid and existing mobile number. You will ensure that

you will not (i) use a business name of another person with an intent to impersonate that

person; (ii) use a business name in which another person has proprietary rights without

such person’s written authorization submitted to support@aqita.in; and (iii) use a

pseudonym or aliases as your business name. In order to connect with the relevant

customers, you can create a profile for your business by providing details like address,

description of business and services, pictures, etc\n

You agree to (a) provide true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself

as required during registration and in your profile and (b) maintain and promptly update

the information to keep it true, accurate, current and complete. If you provide any

information that is untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete, or if the Application

Provider has reasonable grounds to suspect that such information is untrue, inaccurate,

not current or incomplete, the Application Provider has the right to suspend or terminate

your account and/or refuse any or all current or future use of the Licensed Application.

You will solely be responsible for all usage or activity in your account after registration

with the Licensed Application, including use of the account by any third party authorized

by you. You agree that you will not use the Licensed Application to post pornographic

content or content that may be deemed offensive, indecent, or objectionable, which

content may or may not be identified as having explicit language or market, or sell

business, products or services that is illegal. Any fraudulent, abusive, misuse or

otherwise illegal activity may be grounds for removal of such content and/or termination

of your account at the Application Provider’s sole discretion. You will immediately notify

the Application Provider at support@aqita.in of any known or suspected unauthorized

use(s) of your account, or any known or suspected breach of security. The Application

Provider will not be liable for any losses caused to you, whether directly or indirectly for

any unauthorised use of your account or for your failure or delay to intimate the

Application Provider of known or suspected unauthorized use(s) of your account, or any

known or suspected breach of security. You acknowledge, consent and agree that the

Application Provider may access, preserve or disclose your account information,

including but not limited to registration and profile information, financial information such

as bank account details, and related personal information, such as your name, address,

mobile number, date of birth, etc (that you may have to submit in order to receive

payments from the customers), if required to do so by law or in good faith, believing that

such access, preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) comply with legal

process or the order of any Government authority; (b) enforce the Terms and Conditions;

(c) respond to claims that the registration and profile information violates the rights of

third parties; (d) carry out fraud verification in relation to any financial information

provided by you; (e) respond to your requests for customer service; or (f) protect the

rights, property or personal safety of the Application Provider, its users and the public.

You acknowledge and agree that upon your registration and use of the Licensed

Application, the Application Provider will collect, use, store and archive information in

accordance with the aforementioned privacy policy.\n\n

Payment Gateway\n\n

The Licensed Application makes available a payment gateway through its approved

payment processing provider(s). Your use of the payment gateway will be subject to

receiving an approved status by the Application Provider, fulfilling the documentation and

other requirements of the approved payment processing provider(s) and adhering to the

terms and conditions of use prescribed by the payment processing provider(s). Please

contact us at support@aqita.in to understand if you qualify to avail of this service.

You acknowledge and understand that the payment gateway services made available

through the Licensed Application are owned, controlled and provided by the payment

processing provider(s) and hence, the Application Provider does not warrant and in no

way will be liable for the timeliness of such services and the receipt of customer

payments through such services. Termination

\n\nPAYMENT ACTIVATION\n\n

Aqita Business application offers chat services as the default feature for the partner.

Ability to take online payments is subject to additional registration with us based on the

Know Your Customer norms adherence. The policy and requirements to activate payments

for a particular partner is determined by Aqita in accordance with the law of the land.

Businesses which are prohibited by the law for taking online payments is not permitted to

take online payments via Aqita as well. Additionaly, any business, which voilates any law

can be deactivated by us immediately without further notice.

All the online payments going through Aqita will be subject to a fee known as Transaction

Discount Rate (TDR). The TDR applicable to your business will be communicated to you

via Aqita Business application, email, message on the app or any other form of

communication from the Aqita team. In case of any query about the same, you can write

to support@aqita.in

\n\nLicense, Rights and Deactivation\n\n

The license to the Licensed Application is effective until terminated by you or by the

Application Provider in the following circumstances:\n

(i) When you delete your account of your own accord or send an email to

support@aqita.in requiring deletion of your account; (ii) When the Application Provider

ceases to make available the Licensed Application with the provision of 14 days notice.

Additionally, your rights under this license will terminate automatically without notice

from the Application Provider, if you fail to comply with any term(s) set out in these Terms

and Conditions. In such event, the Application Provider reserves the rights to delete your

account and deny you access to the Licensed Application. Upon termination of the

license for any reason, you shall cease all use of the Licensed Application, and destroy all

copies, full or partial, of the Licensed Application.

[Note: Merely un-installing the Licensed Application from your mobile device will not

result in the deletion of your account or information from the Licensed Application and

you will have to send an email to support@aqita.in if you wish to delete your account or

information from the Licensed Application databases and servers.\n\n

Services and Third Party Material\n\n

The Licensed Application enables you to connect with relevant customers of your

business. Use of the Licensed Application requires Internet access on your mobile device.

You understand and acknowledge that the Application Provider only enables you to

connect with the customers who wish to source/procure services from you and does not

provide any guarantees in relation to minimum number of customers, market for your

business, etc. You understand and acknowledge that the Application Provider does not

warrant the suitability of the Licensed Application to conduct your or any third party’s

business through the Licensed Application or the success of such conduct. The

Application Provider disclaims all liability in relation to any transactions, contract or

arrangement entered into between you and the customer(s) through the Licensed

Application, including the delivery of any products or services through the Licensed

Application and will not be responsible for any breach of such contracts or to any claims

for losses, costs, damages, expenses or other legal action arising out of such

transactions, contracts or arrangements.\n

You understand that by using the Licensed Application, you may encounter content that

may be deemed offensive, indecent, or objectionable, which content may or may not be

identified as having explicit language, and that the results of any search or entering of a

particular URL may automatically and unintentionally generate links or references to

objectionable material. Nevertheless, you agree to use the Licensed Application at your

sole risk and that the Application Provider shall not have any liability to you for content

that may be found to be offensive, indecent, or objectionable. You also understand that

any information (including personal information) you may share with any third parties,

customers or other users of the Application Provider’s other licensed applications whilst

using the interactive features of the Licensed Application (such as chat, messaging, etc)

will be solely at your risk as to the security of such information and the Application

Provider cannot guarantee the security of such information or the nature of its use by the

third parties to whom you disclose such information.\n

The Licensed Application may display, include or make available content, data,

information, applications or materials, from third parties, content providers or other users

of the Licensed Applications (collectively and individually called “Third Party Materials”).

By using the Licensed Application, you acknowledge and agree that the Application

Provider is not responsible for examining or evaluating the content, accuracy,

completeness, timeliness, validity, copyright compliance, legality, decency, quality or any

other aspect of such Third Party Materials or web sites. The Application Provider does not

warrant or endorse and does not assume and will not have any liability or responsibility to

you or any other person for any third-Third Party Materials or web sites, or for any other

materials, products, or services of third parties. Before executing any transaction based

upon information obtained from the customers, you should personally verify the accuracy

of such information.

You agree that the Licensed Application contains proprietary content, information and

material that is protected by applicable intellectual property and other laws, including but

not limited to copyright, and that you will not use such proprietary content, information or

materials in any way whatsoever except for permitted use of the Licensed Application.

You agree not to modify, rent, lease, loan, sell, distribute, or create derivative works of the

Licensed Application, in any manner, and you shall not exploit the Licensed Application in

any unauthorized way whatsoever, including but not limited to, by trespass or burdening

network capacity. You further agree not to use the Licensed Application in any manner to

harass, abuse, stalk, bully, threaten, defame, impersonate, gamble, exhibit or transmit

sexually explicit, pornographic, pedophilic content, promulgate hate speech, carry out

illegal activities or otherwise infringe or violate the rights of any other party or other users

of the Licensed Application. You also agree that the Application Provider is not in any way

responsible for any such use by you, nor for any harassing, threatening, defamatory,

offensive or illegal messages or transmissions that you may receive as a result of using

the Licensed Application.\n

The Application Provider makes no representations that the services provided through

the Licensed Application and Third Party Materials are appropriate or available for use in

any particular location. To the extent you choose to access the Licensed Application or

Third Party Materials, you do so at your own initiative and are responsible for compliance

with any applicable laws, including but not limited to applicable local laws. The

Application Provider, and its licensors, reserve the right to change, suspend, remove, or

disable access to the Licensed Application at any time without notice. In no event will the

Application Provider be liable for the removal of or disabling of access to any services

provided through the Licensed Application. The Application Provider may also impose

limits on the use of or access to the customers and services, in any case and without

notice or liability.

\n\nADVERTISEMENTS\n\n

The Application Provider or any third party advertisers may display advertisements and

promotions on the Licensed Application. The manner, mode and extent of advertising by

the Application Provider on the Licensed Application are subject to change. By clicking

on any advertisements you may leave the Licensed Application and be directed to an

external application/website, or to an application/website maintained by an entity other

than the Application Provider. If you decide to visit any such website, you do so at your

own risk and it is your responsibility to take all protective measures to guard against

viruses or other destructive elements. The Application Provider makes no warranty or

representation regarding, and does not endorse, any linked websites or the information

appearing thereon or any of the products or services described thereon.

The Application Provider makes no warranty or representation regarding the

merchantability, fitness for particular purpose, availability, efficacy, reliability, durability

of any product or service advertised on the Licensed Application.

\n\nNO WARRANTY\n\n

YOU EXPRESSLY ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT USE OF THE LICENSED

APPLICATION IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK AND THAT THE ENTIRE RISK AS TO

SATISFACTORY QUALITY, PERFORMANCE, ACCURACY AND EFFORT IS WITH YOU. TO

THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, THE LICENSED

APPLICATION AND ANY SERVICES PERFORMED OR PROVIDED BY THE LICENSED

APPLICATION ("SERVICES") ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" AND “AS AVAILABLE”, WITH ALL

FAULTS AND WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, AND THE APPLICATION PROVIDER

HEREBY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS WITH RESPECT TO THE

LICENSED APPLICATION AND ANY SERVICES, EITHER EXPRESS, IMPLIED OR

STATUTORY, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES AND/OR

CONDITIONS OF MERCHANTABILITY, OF SATISFACTORY QUALITY, OF FITNESS FOR A

PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OF ACCURACY, OF QUIET ENJOYMENT, AND NON-

INFRINGEMENT OF THIRD PARTY RIGHTS. APPLICATION PROVIDER DOES NOT

WARRANT AGAINST INTERFERENCE WITH YOUR ENJOYMENT OF THE LICENSED

APPLICATION, THAT THE FUNCTIONS CONTAINED IN, OR SERVICES PERFORMED OR

PROVIDED BY, THE LICENSED APPLICATION WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS, THAT

THE OPERATION OF THE LICENSED APPLICATION OR SERVICES WILL BE

UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE, OR THAT DEFECTS IN THE LICENSED

APPLICATION OR SERVICES WILL BE CORRECTED. NO ORAL OR WRITTEN

INFORMATION OR ADVICE GIVEN BY APPLICATION PROVIDER OR ITS AUTHORIZED

REPRESENTATIVE SHALL CREATE A WARRANTY. SHOULD THE LICENSED

APPLICATION OR SERVICES PROVE DEFECTIVE, YOU ASSUME THE ENTIRE COST OF

ALL NECESSARY SERVICING, REPAIR OR CORRECTION. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO

NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR LIMITATIONS ON

APPLICABLE STATUTORY RIGHTS OF A CONSUMER, IN SUCH CASES THE ABOVE

EXCLUSION AND LIMITATIONS WILL APPLY TO YOU TO THE EXTENT PERMISSABLE BY

LAW.\n\n

LIMITATION OF LIABILITY\n\n

IN NO EVENT SHALL THE APLLICATION PROVIDER OR ANY OF ITS SUBSIDIARIES OR

AFFILIATES BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY PERSON FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT,

SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR OTHER DAMAGES (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION,

ANY LOST PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, LOSS OF INFORMATION OR

PROGRAMS OR OTHER DATA ON YOUR INFORMATION HANDLING SYSTEM) THAT ARE

RELATED TO THE USE OF, OR THE INABILITY TO USE, THE SERVICES AND FUNCTIONS

OF THE LICENSED APPLICATION OR ANY LINKED WEB SITE/ MOBILE APPLICATION,

EVEN IF THE APPLICATION PROVIDER IS EXPRESSLY ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY

OF SUCH DAMAGES.\n\n

INDEMNITY\n\n

You agree to indemnify and hold harmless the Application Provider, its subsidiaries and

affiliates from any claim, cost, expense, judgment or other loss relating to your use of the

Licensed Application, including without limitation of the foregoing, any action you take

which is in violation of these Terms and Conditions.

\n\nCHOICE OF LAW\n\n

These Terms and Conditions shall be governed by the laws of Republic of India without

giving effect to its conflict of laws provisions. These Terms and Conditions shall be

subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts at Bangalore, India.

\n\nNO THIRD PARTY BENEFICIARIES\n\n

This contract is solely for your benefit and the benefit of Application Provider.

\n\nSEVERABILITY\n\n

If for any reason a court of competent jurisdiction finds any provision or portion of these

Terms and Conditions to be unenforceable, the remainder of these Terms and Conditions

will continue in full force and effect. Please email us at support@aqita.in if you have any

questions regarding these Terms and Conditions.

\n\nANDROID™ TERMS OF USE\n\n

You will be governed by any additional terms of use that may be specified by the

Android™ store or platform from which you downloaded this Licensed Application.

I HAVE READ THE FULL END USER LICENSING AGREEMENT AND AGREE TO ALL OF

THE PROVISIONS CONTAINED ABOVE. I hereby agree to these End User Licensing

Agreement</string>


</resources>
